[
  {
    "question": "What is 1 + 1?",
    "answer": 2,
    "incorrects": [0, 1, 3],
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 2 + 2?",
    "answer": 4,
    "incorrects": [2, 3, 5],
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 5 - 2?",
    "answer": 3,
    "incorrects": [1, 2, 4],
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 2 - 1?",
    "answer": 1,
    "incorrects": [-2, -1, 2],
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 7 * 3?",
    "answer": 21,
    "incorrects": [14, 18, 20],
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 50 * 2?",
    "answer": 100,
    "incorrects": [50, 90, 110],
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 10 / 2?",
    "answer": 5,
    "incorrects": [4, 6, 10],
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "12 / 4?",
    "answer": 3,
    "incorrects": [2, 4, 6],
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 100 / 2?",
    "answer": 50,
    "incorrects": [-50, 40, 60],
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 123 + 234?",
    "answer": 357,
    "incorrects": [355, 356, 358],
    "difficulty": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 134 + 119?",
    "answer": 253,
    "incorrects": [243, 251, 263],
    "difficulty": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 5 - 6?",
    "answer": -1,
    "incorrects": [-2, 0, 1],
    "difficulty": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 5 - (-6)?",
    "answer": 11,
    "incorrects": [-11, -1, 0],
    "difficulty": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is -6 * 8?",
    "answer": -48,
    "incorrects": [-42, 42, 48],
    "difficulty": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is -6 * -8?",
    "answer": 48,
    "incorrects": [-48, -42, 42],
    "difficulty": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 11 * 14?",
    "answer": 154,
    "incorrects": [144, 156, 164],
    "difficulty": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 9 / 2?",
    "answer": 4.5,
    "incorrects": [4, 5, 18],
    "difficulty": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 27 / 4?",
    "answer": 6.75,
    "incorrects": [6, 6.5, 7],
    "difficulty": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 4^3?",
    "answer": 64,
    "incorrects": [36, 49, 74],
    "difficulty": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 1^100?",
    "answer": 1,
    "incorrects": [-1, 100, 1000],
    "difficulty": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the square root of 49?",
    "answer": 7,
    "incorrects": [6, 8, 9],
    "difficulty": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the square root of 81?",
    "answer": 9,
    "incorrects": [7, 8, 10],
    "difficulty": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 193.75 + 102.11",
    "answer": 295.86,
    "incorrects": [294.76, 298.86, 301.75],
    "difficulty": "Hard"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 3828 + 9197",
    "answer": 13025,
    "incorrects": [13005, 13015, 13035],
    "difficulty": "Hard"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 800.7 - 39.65",
    "answer": 761.05,
    "incorrects": [759.88, 769.05, 769.58],
    "difficulty": "Hard"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 550 - 45.8 - (-18.11)",
    "answer": 522.31,
    "incorrects": [486.09, 553.81, 613.91],
    "difficulty": "Hard"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 54 * 12",
    "answer": 648,
    "incorrects": [638, 658, 668],
    "difficulty": "Hard"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 2.2 * 8.9",
    "answer": 19.58,
    "incorrects": [17.58, 18.18, 20.18],
    "difficulty": "Hard"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 118 / 2 / 4",
    "answer": 14.75,
    "incorrects": [15.75, 18.5, 22.5],
    "difficulty": "Hard"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 273.45 / 0.4",
    "answer": 683.625,
    "incorrects": [532.295, 585.495, 628.775],
    "difficulty": "Hard"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 5^4",
    "answer": 625,
    "incorrects": [575, 655, 675],
    "difficulty": "Hard"
  },
  {
    "question": "7^3",
    "answer": 343,
    "incorrects": [323, 339, 353],
    "difficulty": "Hard"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the cubic root of 216",
    "answer": 6,
    "incorrects": [7, 8, 9],
    "difficulty": "Hard"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the 4th root of 81",
    "answer": 3,
    "incorrects": [2, 4, 9],
    "difficulty": "Hard"
  }
]
